https://bellhowell.net/privacy-policy/

Inveloper
LX Feeder Folder (LX-FF)
Mailstar Series
Modular Mailing System (MMS)
Mailing
Automatic Vault System (AVS)
CASS C8000
CASSilo
Card Inspection Sorting System (CISS)
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy is effective as of December 6, 2019.
Bell and Howell’s Commitment to Your Privacy
Bell and Howell (“Company” or “We”) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.
This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit www.bellhowell.net, www.mybellhowell.net and other websites owned by the Company (collectively, the “Sites“) and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information.
This policy applies to information we collect:
On the Sites.
In email, text, and other electronic messages between you and the Sites.
It does not apply to information collected by:
us offline or through any other means; or
collection of data through channels other than the Sites.
Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using the Sites, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of the Sites after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.
If you have any questions about this privacy statement or the content and practices of our Sites, please feel free to contact Bell and Howell directly at:
3791 S. Alston Ave. Durham, NC 27713
Attn: Marketing
800-220-3030
Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It
We collect several types of information from and about users of our Sites, including information:
by which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, or any other information the Sites collect that is defined as personal or personally identifiable information under applicable law (“personal information“);
that is about you but individually does not identify you; and/or
about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Sites and usage details.
We collect this information:
Directly from you when you provide it to us.
Automatically as you navigate through the Site(s). Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies and other tracking technologies.
Information You Provide to Us.  The information we collect on or through our Sites may include:
Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Sites or information you posted to our Sites. This includes information provided when creating an account to access and use our Sites, subscribing to our service, purchasing products, parts and/or services, posting material or responses, or requesting further services or information. We may also ask you for information when you enter a contest or promotion sponsored by us, and when you report a problem with our Sites.
Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us.
Details of transactions you carry out through our Sites and of the fulfillment of your orders. You may be required to provide financial information, such as credit card information, before placing an order through our Sites.
Your search queries on the Sites.
As you navigate through and interact with our Sites, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including, details of your visit to our Sites and information about your computer and internet connection.  The information we collect automatically helps us improve our Sites and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:
Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Sites according to your individual interests.
Speed up your searches
Recognize you when you return to our Sites
Our Sites use a technology called “cookies”.   A cookie is a small piece of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is set to your browser from a Web site’s computers and is stored on your computer’s hard drive.  You may configure your Internet browser not to accept cookies, however, you will not be able to access all features of the Sites if you disable Bell and Howell’s ability to use cookies on your browser.  We may also use cookie-less tracking methods to track your use while on the Sites.
Bell and Howell’s Use of Your Personal Information
We use information collected from users in order to make the Sites more useful and to respond to your queries, to inform users of new promotions, products and services offered by us, to improve our level of service, and to provide notifications regarding the Sites and our products and services.
Within the Company, we restrict access to your personal information to those who require access in order to provide the Sites, products and services to you. We also may share your information with the following entities:
Our affiliates and subsidiaries
Contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business, including Web site hosting companies, fulfillment companies, credit card payment processing companies, and other third-party service providers;
To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of a bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by the Company about our Sites’ users is among the assets transferred; and
Government agencies and law enforcement officials, when required to do so to respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process, or to establish or exercise or legal rights or defend against legal claims.
Bell and Howell also reserves the right to share Information with other organizations in the following situations:
As permitted by law in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, violation of our intellectual property rights, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Site’s Terms of Use or other agreements, or otherwise as required by law.
When we have your consent to do so; and
When we need to share Information to provide any product or service you have requested.
The Company also may use your IP address and information about the Web pages you visit to gather broad demographic information, interests and behavior so that we may better understand our customers and Site users. This information may be used, for example, to analyze and improve our Site design and functionality. The Company may share aggregated demographic, product usage, or traffic pattern information for marketing purposes with other organizations, but these statistics will not include information that identify you personally.
Opt-out Policy
When you provide personal information via our Sites, we may use the personal information to occasionally notify you about special Bell and Howell sales or services and other valuable updates to personalize your Bell and Howell shopping transactions. If you prefer that we not contact you in this manner, we will promptly remove you from our mailing list at your request.
Please send any such request to:
3791 S. Alston Ave. Durham, NC 27713
Attn: Marketing
800-220-3030
How to Review and Update Your Information
We provide methods of updating your personal information and contact preferences. In some cases, these will be automated via our Sites. You also may write or telephone us with changes to your information and contact preferences at:
3791 S. Alston Ave. Durham, NC 27713
Attn: Marketing
800-220-3030
Security
We use a variety of standard protections to maintain the security of your online session. Although the Sites have security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your information under our control, we cannot guarantee that such security measures will be sufficient, will not be breached, and that your information may not be disclosed or otherwise accessed in any unauthorized manner. Certain information may be transmitted to you by electronic mail. Although it may be illegal to intercept or disclose these messages, these transmissions are not secured.
California Consumer Privacy Act Rights
As of January 1, 2020 verified California residents have the right:
To request and receive disclosure of our personal information collection practices during the prior twelve (12) months, including the categories of personal information we collect, the categories of sources of such information, our business purpose for collecting or sharing such information, and the categories of third parties with whom we share such information.
To request and receive a copy of the personal information we have collected about them during the prior twelve (12) months.
To request that we delete (and, to the extent applicable, direct our service providers to delete) their personal information subject to certain exceptions.
In order to make a request for disclosure, please contact us at
3791 S. Alston Ave. Durham, NC 27713
800-220-3030
In connection with a request from you pertaining to the foregoing, we will ask you for information that allows us to reasonably verify your identity (that you are the person about whom we collected personal information) and will use that information only for that purpose. We cannot respond to your request or provide you with personal information if we cannot verify your identity and confirm that the personal information relates to you.
You may make a request up to twice within a twelve (12) month period. We will endeavor to respond within forty-five (45) days of receipt of your request, but if we require more time (up to an additional forty-five (45) days) we will notify you of our need for additional time.
For requests for a copy of the personal information we have collected during the twelve (12) months prior to your request, we will endeavor to provide the information in a format that is readily useable, including by mailing you a paper copy.
We will not discriminate against you as a result of your exercise of any of these rights.
Children’s Privacy Protection
The Sites do not target children or provide products or services for use by children. We do not knowingly collect information from persons under 13 years of age. If you are under 13 years of age, you may review the Sites only with involvement of a parent or guardian, and you may not use any portion of the Sites that would require collection of personal information from you.
Linked Internet Web sites
The Site may provide hypertext links to other Web sites that may contain privacy provisions that are different from those provided herein. We are not responsible for the collection, use or disclosure of information collected through those Web sites, and we expressly disclaim any and all liability related to such collection, use or disclosure. You are encouraged to read the privacy policies of Web sites reached through the use of links from the Site.
Modification
This privacy policy may be updated periodically and without prior notice to you to reflect changes in our online information practices. We will indicate at the top of the policy when it was most recently updated. We recommend that you visit our Privacy Policy page whenever you visit the Sites so that you are aware of any changes.
How to Contact Us
If you have any questions or complaints about our Site, our privacy policy or the Information we collect, please contact us at:
3791 S. Alston Ave. Durham, NC 27713
Attn: Marketing
800-220-3030
Privacy/Protection When Ordering from Us
Policy does not cover information that is inherent to the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond the control of Bell and Howell, LLC, and is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation.
Bell and Howell Headquarters
3791 South Alston Ave
Durham, NC 27713
info@bhemail.com
©2020 Bell and Howell, LLC. All rights reserved.
Discover
Automated Equipment Services
Products & Solutions
Contact Us
About
Our Company
Executive Team
Careers
Inveloper
LX Feeder Folder (LX-FF)
Mailstar Series
Modular Mailing System (MMS)
IQ Production
IQ Item
JETVision®
Producer 400EVO
Producer Series DM
ProducerTM Series
Rigid Mailer
SmartMailer
SnapPack Pressure Sealer
SnapPack Cold Glue Systems
Secure Cards & Storage
Secure Storage
Mailing
Automatic Vault System (AVS)
CASS C8000
CASSilo
Card Inspection Sorting System (CISS)
About Us
Executive Team
Careers
Resources
Press Releases
Document Library
Blog
Contact Us
Support
We have updated our privacy policy with respect to the collection and use of your personal information. At any time, you can learn about your rights by going to the Privacy Policy section of the website.OkPrivacy policy
